Support Admin Watch on
kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
THIS IS A WORK OF FICTION.
CHILD ACTORS AND ANIMALS WERE FILMED
IN ACCORDANCE WITH SAFETY GUIDELINES.
BASED ON THE ORIGINAL SERIES "LA MANTE"
PRODUCED BY JEAN NAINCHRICK
AUGUST 17, 1998
MINERS' HOUSING,
HYUPSEONG, WOONGSAN
We received a report of a child screaming.
May I take a look inside?
My son just never listens to me.
I raised my voice a bit,
and he begged for forgiveness, crying.
Satisfied?
We've received several reports.
I already told you.
That goddamn brat just never listens
to a single word I say.
So what?
Are you going to take him and raise him?
Sir, there's no need for all that.
Unless it involved a flagrant offender,
the police lack authority
to compel an investigation.
Refusal to answer questions
isn't punishable under any provision.
It's this way, sir.
They said a little kid
was discovered staring at the body.
With a smile on his face.
Now, let's go to the police station.
Okay.
You can follow me.
POLICE
What were you doing
around 7 p.m. last night?
I left work around six, and…
I took a shower and got ready for dinner.
- What your wife mentioned…
- Yes, that's right.
The signal is strong.
Once the hostage exchange is completed,
all units will move in.
All units, around the mountain.
No, that can't happen.
The safety of the hostage
hasn't been secured yet.
Once it is, then they can swarm in.
All will stand by
and await further command.
Let me repeat. All will stand by
Hyuk.
Circle behind the mountain and search
Mine Number Two from the back now.
Yes, ma'am.
Maintain a clear field of vision,
and keep yourself concealed.
Where are they?
We have a full house.
As soon as the exchange happens,
our units will move in.
Take your shot
as soon as Jung-yeon is safe.
What?
Wait.
Go. Run.
Mother.
Thank you.
Hey, Mom.
Move it.
Exchange complete.
Jung-yeon is safe.
Let's move in.
Su-yeol.
Jung-yeon.
Run.
Run if you don't want to die.
- Jung-yeon.
- Safety first. Take it slow.
Take off the tracker first.
We lost the tracker signal.
What?
What's the last known location?
Don't pretend to be weak.
Keep walking.
The police couldn't care less
if I live or die.
You're right.
What the fuck?
I'll check it out.
You head to the hospital.
Those fucking pricks.
Fuck.
Run. You need to run.
Jung-yeon.
You'll be okay.
We'll be at the hospital soon.
What about Mother?
Arrived at the miners' rest area.
No one to report.
Hey, guys. Keep up the good work.
I checked over there already.
How can we trust Jeong I-shin's son?
Return to the office now!
The test result came back positive
for mifepristone, an abortion drug.
But fortunately,
it was a small amount. You should be fine.
What about the baby?
Shall we take a look?
That's the baby's heartbeat.
Its heartbeat…
Su-yeol.
Your mother kept trying to protect me.
Wait.
Go.
Run.
Take your shot
as soon as Jung-yeon is safe.
Jung-yeon.
By any chance, do you remember anything?
The spot where you were held captive.
There was this strong,
sickening metallic smell in the air.
I heard creaking sounds.
It looked like some storage room
without any windows.
There were machine parts around.
And I remember seeing
the word, "Start"…
Anything else?
Well…
"King"?
I remember reading
something ending with "king" on the wall.
And the floor
felt like really old cement.
Yeah, I remember feeling cement powder.
I'm sure of it.
Su-yeol.
Go and find Mother.
Ah-ra…
She's completely insane.
Mother is in danger.
You just had to bring the police with you.
Listen.
I was so disappointed.
The old, feeble Mantis is now reduced
to the pitiful task
of fretting over her damn kid.
Is your son that important?
I mean,
what do you even know about
your son anyway?
Your son bent over backwards
to pretend like you didn't exist.
Then again,
it wasn't just your son.
The whole world doesn't know you exist.
They all forgot about you.
You should give it a go.
It'll bring you such peace.
It's pretty nice.
No.
I am the only one
who hasn't forgotten about you.
I am also the only one
who finds you commendable.
It was you who removed my dad,
the man who used to sear my nose
to "cast the demons away,"
from my life.
You punished every despicable beast
you came across.
It was just so freaking cool.
I was obsessed with you.
It was as if…
you were Joan of Arc
carrying around Medusa's head.
So I followed in your footsteps.
I modeled myself after you.
I am you.
You made me.
So please, take some responsibility.
Mom.
Why did you do it?
What?
Hey.
At the very least,
you should've shown me some love.
My dad thought I was a monster,
but you saved me!
Why did you act so irresponsibly?
Doesn't it get so lonely?
Living as a monster…
You can never go back home.
It's okay.
I'll embrace you.
I understand you.
We are creatures
who can never return to society.
The line drawn by shitty society…
We've crossed it so long ago.
Who even knows when and how we did that?
I know
Just like you,
I have nowhere to go.
So let's make sure
we don't betray each other.
Mom.
Don't kid yourself.
I'm not the one who betrayed you.
What?
You searched for prey as Jo-i on an app.
You never looked elsewhere to hunt.
So goddamn lazy.
After you killed your prey,
you couldn't even do the bare minimum
and delete their profiles.
You let down your hair
for the cops to climb.
You have no one to blame
except yourself
for letting that hair drag.
Is that so? Fuck.
The police are on their way.
Thanks to your bloody footsteps.
What's this?
Are you worried about me?
Yeon-joong.
Did you drag me all the way here
just to profess your love for me?
You're running out of time.
This is your one chance
if you want to kill me.
Go on.
Is that so?
Fine.
You and I both die here.
Is that what you're proposing?
You know, I just thought about it.
Yeah, this sort of ending…
It's not a bad idea.
At the end of the day,
with you by my side, nothing scares me.
Damn it.
That stings.
What are you looking for?
Save your breath.
You don't have long.
Oh, I get it.
The full Mantis treatment at last,
carved alive with my breath intact.
If the police arrive a bit early,
you might make it.
It won't be easy, though.
Where are you going?
Don't go.
Are you going to abandon me?
I don't believe Joan of Arc
beheaded Medusa.
Who the hell cares who did it?
You'll grow cold quite quickly
when you lose a lot of blood.
I saw all of them
tremble so.
Are you going back to prison? Why?
Why the hell would you do that?
Don't go.
Please don't go back.
There's a way out
the police don't know about.
I know where it is.
I'll make sure you get out of here
without getting caught.
I'll show you.
I can give you freedom.
So please…
Stop trying to run away already.
It'd be a hassle.
I'll take the main road.
Open it.
Didn't I tell you?
I know you through and through.
See.
I didn't forget.
A storage room for machine parts?
ANTICIPATED ROUTE
There's no such facility near the mines.
What about here?
What was this area used for?
Oh, that?
They built an amusement park there
when the mines were doing well.
It's been shut down for a while now.
I'm not sure you'll find anything there.
I remember reading
something ending with "king" on the wall.
"King."
"Viking"?
CHA SU-YEOL
POLICE AGENCY
You're one step too late.
Jeong I-shin just left.
There's a secret passageway, you see.
Where could she have gone?
Back to prison?
Give up.
Even if you shoot me now,
you'll be caught in the end.
Everyone's headed here.
Tell me
where Jeong I-shin went.
Cha Su-yeol.
You know so little about Jeong I-shin.
And I guess you'll die ignorant.
Goodbye, Cha Su-yeol.
Detective Kim!
Where's Jeong I-shin?
She's not here.
She's disappeared.
She escaped through a secret passageway.
- But first--
- Inspector Cha Su-yeol.
Go and catch Jeong I-shin.
Go and bring her back.
I'll be sure to.
DON'T FORGET YOUR FAMILY
WANTS YOU TO PUT SAFETY FIRST
LEADING COAL INDUSTRY INNOVATION!
EAST MINE SHAFT
Set one up all the way over there.
And check this area.
Wait, Kim.
Are you okay?
Are you sure you're okay?
- Wait.
- Yeah?
- Ji-an, I'm going to go with her.
- Yes?
Call the chief now.
- Update him on the situation.
- Okay.
Kang Yeon-joong, the culprit
behind the serial murders,
was shot dead by the police
at the end of their relentless pursuit.
The motive
is currently being investigated.
The 140,000 police officers
of the Republic of Korea
will always strive to put the safety
of the people they serve first.
MAJOR CRIMES INVESTIGATION UNIT
NAMBU METROPOLITAN POLICE AGENCY
BLOCKED NUMBER
Su-yeol?
How's Detective Kim?
Her surgery went well. She's stable.
An off-the-record APB
has been issued for you two.
You know, don't you?
Don't worry.
I will bring that woman back.
Where are you?
You don't need to do it alone.
Let's find her together. Okay?
Sir.
Why were you so lenient with her?
And with me?
I understand that was the deal negotiated.
But even so…
I've always wondered about that.
Why did you do all that?
On a human level,
I never thought
what Jeong I-shin did was wrong.
Why not?
You're a cop.
I was only a cop
when I caught her
and boasted about such achievements.
I failed everywhere else.
Within the bounds of the law,
I wanted to make her life easier.
My personal feelings toward her
created a rift within my heart.
And that rift
led me to make that choice.
When I look at you now,
I think I made the right decision.
Pull yourself together, Mister.
Jeong I-shin
is just another murderer.
Her victims just happened
to be criminals themselves.
We failed to stop any crimes
or save anyone.
Whether it's one person or five,
it is the police's job
to save lives.
At times, we may fail
and fall into cowardice,
but in the end, it's up to us.
It's up to the police.
Su-yeol.
It seems you grew overly sentimental
while stalling to allow tracking.
Old geezer.
POWER OFF
Cha Su-yeol.
You know so little
about Jeong I-shin.
Peek-a-boo.
I came here on the off chance,
and you're here.
Detective Bae.
Why are you at Kang's house?
You think you'll find something?
Will it help you find Jeong I-shin?
Yes, wait… What about Detective Kim?
She lucked out. She's surprisingly fine.
What kind of spell
did you put on her, anyway?
As soon as she woke up, she told me
to go and help you out.
Let's give it a go.
I'll work my magic
and get you that opening.
It's freezing out here.
Hey.
You guys had dinner, right?
Not yet.
The culprit has been caught.
They're making you suffer for nothing, no?
The homeowner is dead.
Come on. Let's go.
Let's grab some dinner.
A BODY DISCOVERED IN NODU STREAM
LOG IN
JEONG I-SHIN, HYPNOTHERAPY 1-1
MAY 13, 2003
Just ease into a relaxed state.
Let yourself release all tension.
There is a window.
We're going to open that window now.
There is another world
outside that window.
It is beyond the conscious.
On the far side of awareness.
It is the world of the subconscious.
You will now lift your hand
and slowly open that window.
I don't want to.
I can't.
You're okay.
I'll be right by your side.
HYPNOTHERAPY 3-3
MAY 13, 2003
It's dark.
The sky is dark.
It's nighttime, but there's a bird flying.
It's weird. The sun is up,
but it's dark.
No.
The sun is up, and so is the moon.
Even stars.
I just look at them.
I…
I'm just going to keep looking at them.
Why do you only look at them?
No, that's my choice.
I'm just going to look at them.
Last night, in my dreams
I put on wings
and flew up higher than the clouds
as I soared up into the sky
I smell it.
It put something on my face.
Makeup.
Why do you think that happened?
It says I'm a grown-up.
No. I see the sun,
the moon, and the stars.
I'm flying.
I fly away and away.
I fly away to flee.
From what?
That thing.
That thing killed my mother.
That thing burned my mother to death.
What is…
"that thing"?
That thing is touching me.
Can you tell me what "that thing" is?
Dad!
THANK YOU, PASTOR JEONG HYUN-NAM
Wait…
SHARING A MEAL OF LOVE
FREE MEAL SERVICE
Hey, Dad.
It's been a while.
My beautiful daughter.
It's because
Daddy loves you so much.
What is going on here?
What did you do?
How can you even call yourself human?
I-shin…
My poor I-shin.
She's your daughter!
You're scum.
What did you do to your daughter?
I didn't do anything. Damn it.
You scum.
How could you do that to I-shin?
Come here.
- Let go of me!
- Come here.
I-shin.
I-shin!
Let go of me, you bastard!
Let go!
- Let go. I-shin!
- Come here!
I'm going to report you to the police.
Why you…
I-shin…
I-shin… Run…
- I-shin…
- Mom…
I-shin…
I-shin, run…
JUSIN CHURCH
THANK YOU, PASTOR JEONG HYUN-NAM
Back then,
as our house was burning down,
you told me,
"Now that Mom's gone,
from now on,
you have to take over for her."
Why are you doing this?
It has been over 20 years.
I did you wrong.
I have prayed for forgiveness endlessly.
And after countless hours
of praying to the Lord,
I received my calling from him.
That's how I became a pastor.
And for the sake of repentance,
I took in poor kids who had nowhere to go.
I changed every dirty diaper,
and raised them all by myself!
Did you raise them
the way you raised me?
No, that didn't happen.
I am a servant of the Lord.
That never happened with them.
I was forgiven.
Killing me
won't undo the past.
The Lord has forgiven me.
He even forgave you.
You have been forgiven as well.
What choice do we have?
We only have our bloodline to blame.
We have been forgiven.
We are clean now.
It's not because of that damn bloodline!
Not that damn bloodline!
It's you.
You just did it because you wanted to.
Forgiveness?
Who would dare?
Forgive who?
How dare they?
Even after I killed
all those repugnant pieces of shit,
I have never once
even dreamt about being forgiven.
How dare you?
Who the hell are you
to expect forgiveness from anyone?
Please spare me.
Dear daddy,
let's just end it here.
It's time you and I
put an end to all of this.
Stop!
Don't move.
Put down the knife.
Put it down!
Step back.
Su-yeol.
Su-yeol, you must act now.
You must shoot this demonic wench now.
You can do that, right?
Shut up.
You can still spew such bullshit?
You!
You told me the same thing every day.
"Your mother is the devil."
"Your mother is possessed
by an evil spirit."
I believed those words
and that's why!
Su-yeol, that's a misunderstanding.
I did that for your sake.
Shut it.
Or I can shoot you right now.
Let's go.
Come with me.
Don't let
those hands see more blood.
Please.
Su-yeol, hurry up and get her out of here.
- Why?
- No, it's not true.
- You can't.
- Su-yeol.
No, she did it because she wanted to.
She was curious.
Su-yeol, you can't.
Don't become like me.
Please don't.
You can't, Su-yeol.
You can't cross that line.
Su-yeol, wake up!
Su-yeol!
You need to save me!
- Be quiet.
- You're a cop!
- You talk too much.
- Su-yeol!
- It's over. Be quiet!
Why are you so noisy?
Just be quiet already.
Stop talking!
We have caused that kid
way too much suffering already.
JUSIN CHURCH
THANK YOU, PASTOR JEONG HYUN-NAM
You go outside.
Mom!
Eun-ae, get back in the house. Go on.
Quickly.
NEW FAITH CHILD WELFARE CENTER
Jeong I-shin.
Jeong I-shin!
Wake up, Jeong I-shin!
Jeong I-shin.
Wake up.
Jeong I-shin!
You can't leave like this.
Mom.
Mom!
Please don't leave me.
Please.
Wake up!
Mom.
Are you okay?
Take a deep breath.
JUSIN CHURCH
Jung-yeon and I'll come to visit.
They should allow visits.
Don't. Forget me.
Just live your life as you always have.
I'll still come for a visit.
You're my mom.
Inspector Cha Su-yeol.
You got it all wrong.
Bloodlines are meaningless.
How you lived your life is what matters.
You led a life different from mine.
You made an effort
and became a police officer
to save lives.
Each step left its mark on you.
So…
you're not like me at all.
I like that about you.
Eun-ae.
Jung-yeon's condition improved
and she's been discharged. Go home to her.
Okay.
Ms. Jeong I-shin.
I'll be escorting you to prison.
Let's go.
Captain Cha.
You're certainly a man of your word.
CHA SU-YEOL
POLICE AGENCY
Did you come all this way
to confirm that? In that state?
I guess I did.
Thanks.
I heard you asked
Detective Bae to help me.
No need. We're all on the same team.
But, who's this?
She'll be coming with me.
There will be some commotion for a while.
And…
the benefits you've received until now
and the rest of your conditions
will be rescinded.
And you'll be questioned
on suspicion of parricide.
Yes.
I understand.
Chief Choi.
Inherent compassion.
Tender mercy.
Jeong-ho possesses such traits.
You kept your promise to me.
Thank you.
I didn't do much.
He raised himself.
And I managed
to get this for you.
A photo of Su-yeol.
When he was a freshman in high school,
one of his classmates was disabled.
That classmate was being bullied in class…
My goodness.
That was quite a detour.
Detective Kim.
You should return to the hospital now.
Don't you dare
have a team dinner without me
just because I'm gone.
Gosh. That would never happen.
Detective Bae without Detective Kim?
That'd be unbearable.
Hey, watch it.
I quit alcohol.
I'm reborn now.
What's your name?
Eun-ae.
Do you want to come with me?
They say while I was gone,
Su-yeol tried to protect
the weak around him.
Even without your mom,
you grew up strong,
to stand on your own.
Take care,
Inspector Cha Su-yeol.
All my questions about you
have been answered now.
2 YEARS LATER
ANWON PRISON,
ANWON, GYEONGGI PROVINCE
Previously, Park had even proposed
doing it as a live broadcast.
The two sides have agreed to present
just their opening statements.
Their agenda is
to be arranged at a later date.
All eyes are on whether
the repeatedly postponed meeting
between the party leaders
will finally materialize.
On to the next story.
Around 2 a.m. yesterday,
a local resident discovered
a heavily mutilated body in a mountain
near Sinyang-dong, Seoul.
The body was identified
as Chief Superintendent Choi Jung-ho
of Sanghyeon Police.
He was known
for his significant contribution
to the arrest of Kang Yeon-joong,
the culprit behind the Nodu Stream Murder,
among others, two years ago.
The body was transported to the NFS…
Inmate 2067, you have a visitor.
- Come out.
- Through today's press conference…
What happened?
And then, proceed to…
"I'll be in touch."
Let's go, Queen Mantis!
Subtitle translation by: Justin S. Kim